<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Morry Method]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Morry Method]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-morry-method/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:19:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/the-morry-method/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9f6e4d96-5598-4c35-8798-201fda9cf22d.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-morry-method/the-morry-methodtm-breaking-news-read-the-latest-indepe/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">642cbbb0-6cb4-4d87-a912-f2d189a6d6a3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:19:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Morry Method™ ***Breaking News*** Read the latest independant research further proving the efficacy of "The Morry Method" by clicking HERE "An Experimental Intervention for Reducing Math Anxiety and Fostering Positive Social Change" by Dr. Glenroy Pinnock MSc, London University College, 2007 BSc, University of the West Indies, 2002                    ——————————   I invite you to listen to my new show "Mind Power, With Morry Zelcovitch" LIVE on KAZM Radio AM780 in Sedona, Arizona Thursday Mornings at 11:15am EST. The show is all about you, and how you can literally use the power of your mind to live the life of your dreams, truly be happy and so much more. I'll be dealing with relevant and varied topics each week to help you to empower yourself by gaining a new understanding of your reality and by doing so positively influence it regardless of what might be happening around you! To listen live simply click the following link and then the "Listen Live" banner at the top of the page... http://www.kazmradio.com If your not in the Eastern Time Zone then feel free to click here for a time converter. If you want to listen at your leisure by streaming or downloading a podcast of the show then please feel free to click here.                  —————————— Welcome to "The Morry Method™". Depending on how you came to land here, you may be familiar with The Morry Method™ (TMM), and you may even be one of  the many who has enjoyed the benefits of TMM at use in Quantum Mind Power and Quantum Confidence.  Whether or not you are new to The Morry Method™, I would like to take this opportunity to review just how different this proprietary technology is to any other brainwave entrainment program or tool available … anywhere.  Not only is The Morry Method™ the result of decades of study and research, but as one of the few Certified Brainwave Entrainment Engineers on the planet, I can state with certainty that there is no truer or deeper method of brainwave entrainment shared, publicly or otherwise, nor provided with more consideration for the 'end user' experience.  The Morry Method's proprietary protocol for presenting various stimuli to the brain and mind results in an experience that is much “softer” on the brain and body sytem. There is a more natural incorporation of the “brain beats” with all their associated benefits, as well as any other presented information such as meditations or affirmations. My goal is to bring the proven benefits of brainwave entrainment to everyone. If your life is nothing but joyful, The Morry Method™ can provide a pleasurable enhancement to take it up a notch. More importantly, if you are struggling with any aspect of your life — or if you are living with stress in any of it's incarnations — The Morry Method™ of brainwave entrainment can help.  The Brazilian Government and a major Brazilian University research study seem to agree.  All The Morry Method™ recordings are mixed to ensure a harmonic balance of sound, science and technology — a combination that provides the maximum effects possible. They also folllow a strict adherence to comprehensive scientific research.  Real Science. Real Results. I’m here for you.  Morry Zelcovitch Certified Brainwave Entrainment Engineer</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.themorrymethod.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">befbe5af-4af5-4cd5-b2f3-e2da8c825a0d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:19:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>